There's nothing Yoshikage
Kira despises more than
sticking out in a crowd or
being the center of attention.
To think I'd suffer such a sickening
humiliation in front of total strangers.
What's going on?
Heart attack pilots itself?
How could it be ensnared?
I have no idea what's
causing this to happen,
but I have to reverse
it before it's too late.
How's it going down there, buddy?
Can we help you out?
You don't look like you're doing so good.
I can call your mama for you if you want.
How about it?
I'm just fine.
Now beat it.
Yo, did you catch what this dude said?
It looks like he had too much booze,
and now this sloppy drunk has
forgotten how to use his manners.
Yeah, you enjoying the buzz?
Nice suit you got there!
Me and my home dog just got
fired and we're flat broke.
The ladies ain't exactly lining up either,
so when I see broskies
like you, I get agitated!
Don't just lie there!
Would you look at that!
Your shoelaces are untied.
Let me take care of that for you.
What a knot!
Good luck getting them
suckers loose again!
Oh, shitballs, what the hell did that?
It was a bomb made by my stand's power,
and that was Deadly Queen's Bomb Type 1.
What are you doing, you fool?
Today has been a complete disaster.
All Yoshikage Kira wanted to do
was live a simple, quiet life.
But those meddling
maggots just had to stick
their wretched noses
where they didn't belong.
Thank you.
I always chase you, I always chase you.
I don't want to run away.
I'll do it again!
The future is the end,
so I chase you.
What happened at that shoe shop?
I'm still kind of confused.
Koichi couldn't really explain it over
the phone, but it didn't sound good.
Let's hurry.
It'll take about five
minutes to get there.
You managed to crack it.
And if the bomb stand took damage, then
its user just got a nasty surprise too.
Please do not venture
too far from my side.
And so you're aware, my
range is five meters.
I can see this comes as a shock to you.
Make no mistake, we've indeed matured.
Our power is much greater than before.
My inferior range in comparison with
Act 2 is an unavoidable shortcoming.
Moving outside my 5 meter range removes
the weight applied to the target object.
If it does so,
the target will be excited
to such a degree that
it will rush toward us
like an animal in heat.
Conversely, if your aim
is to pin the target down,
moving closer will exponentially increase
the amount of force applied to it.
So what's it going to be?
Neither.
For now I want him right there.
I just hope Josuke gets here
before Trouble shows up.
You know, I hear a new gym is getting
ready to open near Budogaoka High School.
And given today's events,
I'm now considering joining.
I should probably build up my strength.
Then again, I haven't
had the best luck lately.
I could end up sharing weights with or
swimming in the same pool as the dregs?
who'd rather play with
their dicks than bathe.
It took me a total of
three minutes to get here.
I realized the full extent of my weakness
as I tried to traverse the crosswalk.
Question for you.
How many guests should I be
expecting to join this party?
What?
You phone someone asking for help, right?
Josuke Higashikata and
Okuyasu Nijimura are closest,
and being about five minutes away,
I'd wager they have two minutes to go.
You're one of their best
friends, are you not?
Wait.
Yukako Yamagishi and that
haughty woman who runs
Beauty Institute Cinderella
are stand users as well, right?
Though I severely doubt you'd turn to
them for help in your hour of need.
You're the killer!
In all the confusion, I
misplaced my other jacket.
No matter, I'll retrieve it later.
But first, I must do away with you.
I was right!
You're the man we're all after!
You're the killer!
Year after year, you've killed people.
I doubt you even remember them all.
Reimi? Shigechi?
Shigechi?
Make him suffer, Act Three!
Deadly Queen.
That's so not fair!
Why does this guy have two stands?
I thought a user could only possess one!
While Deadly Queen is my actual stand,
Heart Attack is a smart bomb which
I launch from the stand's left hand.
That's why the damage I've received
has been contained to my left hand.
Before we proceed, Master Koichi,
you should know that you've just left
the parameters of the 5-meter range.
The force suppressing his
bomb stand will dissipate.
Finally.
S-H-I-T.
Since it has escaped, I will have
to initiate three frees again.
How interesting.
Your stand's range is limited.
Which of them shall be
the target of my attack?
The actual murderer or that
piece-of-shit bomb stand?
Unfortunately, Master, three frees
cannot weigh down two targets at once.
Even if we immobilize the user,
the bomb stand will just keep
charging at us on autopilot.
But if we stop the bomb, the
user will rush in for the kill.
Which will it be, sir?
I need your orders before it's too late.
To whom shall I direct my attack?
Find your target is the bomb!
Free! Freeze!
Goodness.
A valiant effort,
but it appears you were
destined for defeat
no matter which of us
you decided to target.
I used to think Heart Attack was
my invincible ace in the hole.
I never imagined it would be
rendered completely ineffective.
What a day.
I had to compensate a cafe, and
then I had a run-in with some thugs.
Truthfully, I feel like
I've been taken for a ride.
This is a first for me.
Never have I been so
challenged in such a way.
In fact, I've been left with a
slight taste of defeat in my mouth.
Well, you've certainly earned
my deepest respects, boy.
You really are something else.
By the way, you wouldn't happen to
have any tissues on hand, would you?
A handkerchief would also do.
What is this?
I've gone out of my way
to pay you my respects.
The least you could do
was converse with me.
I don't have any.
No worries.
Feel free to use mine.
Quickly now, your nose is gushing blood.
I offered it so you
could clean yourself up.
I'm about to beat you
into a bloody puddle.
And in just over a minute, your
friends will arrive to find nothing.
Leaving you alive just
doesn't sit right with me.
Especially after the public
humiliation I endured.
Oh, put a sock in it.
Better yet, why not take the whole foot?
This day has gifted me with the
exact same pain you're feeling now.
However,
I accepted it with grace as opposed to
your tedious whining, you mewling Cameo.
Sit back and watch a real man work.
See?
Tissues come in handy, don't they?
Here, let me.
Blood or otherwise, they say a stuffy
nose is a sure path to slow cognition.
If it's any consolation,
not too long ago, I was groveling
on the ground just like you.
In one minute, I will vaporize
you with Deadly Queen.
Until then, why don't you learn from
yours truly and put up with the pain?
Learn to be tough in
the face of resistance!
What do you know?
Your name is...
is Yoshikage Kira!
You look surprised.
All I did was say your name, Kira.
You gotta look at my driver's license,
but when did you have the
chance to bill for my wallet?
you pathetic little bootlicker?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
You reimbursed the cafe.
You couldn't have given me
a better clue if I'd asked.
I don't see how the two are related.
Regardless, learning my name
now does you a little good.
In a matter of moments,
you'll cease to exist.
Yeah, believe me, I know all
too well what's about to happen.
But even so, if a pathetic bootlicker like
me can figure out your name that easily,
I guess you're not as tough
as you seem to think you are.
Sure, you might get away for the
time being, but you know what, Kira?
I bet your every thought
is mocking me for letting
a whiny brat unravel the
mystery of your name.
And if they aren't, I'll
do the honors for them.
A mewling little high
School just found you out.
You're such a colossal dumbass!
I'll be waiting for you on the other
side, you murder-happy son of a bitch!
That's enough!
That's the end of that brat.
But damn him, why do I feel like I lost?
What an infuriating pest.
I let him provoke me, but I still have a
minute before Josuke and Okuyasu show up.
I thought roughing the boy up
would settle my turbulent spirit,
but I can't say I feel much better.
Huh?
Why would he be wearing
his socks inside out?
I guess it doesn't bother him.
No!
I can't stand it!
That's the wrong way!
But the shoe store is this way!
This path will get us there faster!
Hurry!
Put your damn socks on right!
That gnawing unease is gone.
Which means it's time to eradicate
you like the bug you are!
Deadly queen!
The tip of this figure can transform
anything it touches into a bomb.
So for your execution, I think I'll
have it transform your student badge.
Bomb type one!
You did a good job holding
down the fork, Koichi.
I'll take it from here.
What?!
This is a shock.
I didn't think you'd be able to prop
yourself up with those injuries.
You would have been
better off entering your
eternal slumber peacefully on the ground.
I'm fairly certain I can see the trees
behind you through your gaping wounds.
Nice watch. Huh?
Go ahead and take one last look at
it, because I'm about to bust it up.
To be clear, by it, I mean your face.
You certainly are an
intriguing individual.
I would love to learn your
name, among other things,
but I really must mosey
along to my next destination.
I have a mere 20 seconds left.
Mindless small talk just
isn't on the agenda.
I have to be honest with you.
Your stans attack was surprisingly feeble.
Stopping that pitiful punch was
like catching a little pup fly.
You'd have to be an absolute
Neanderthal to believe your
feebleness has any chance of
overcoming Deadly Queen's power.
What the hell?
How can you move so fast?
Good freaking grief. I take it back.
Up close that watch is tacky as hell.
Although to be fair, I'd say that's
the least of your worries now.
Well, there's something that's going to
look a lot worse than that piece of junk.
And that, my friend, is your putrid face.
What is this, Dan?
It's so fast, it's like the
damn thing has stopped time!
Koichi, if you hadn't stepped up the way
you did, I would have been long dead.
Even all alone, you fought
valiantly right up to the end.
There's no doubt about it, you've matured.
You have my respect.
Hey, Koichi! Koichi!
Oh no!
Did we get here too late?
What happened?
Hey, Koichi!
Jotaro, hang on!
Eyes open Okuyasu yeah sure but what
the hell how'd they get so messed
up calm down we have to find out if
they're still alive if they are i can
heal them with shining diamond yes
jotaro's alive but he's barely clinging
to life koichi is too but he's not
breathing you gotta hurry up and heal
him, Josuke!
He's not gonna make it at this rate!
I can't believe it.
Josuke and Okuyasu
are here.
This is the worst day
I've ever lived through.
It's been one disaster after another.
Yoshikage Kira has always been able to
overcome any obstacle
that's gotten in his way.
And
I'll get out of this mess as well.
I must!
Where are you going?
Look at him.
He got beat to shit.
Listen, turn around and don't try
anything funny. You got it? What's wrong?
Didn't you hear what he said?
Show us your face!
Be careful, you two!
You have to stay far away
from Mukadeya's shoes!
Another crazy explosion
might go off! Get to safety!
The first one came out of nowhere
and blew the owner to pieces!
They were caught up in it, too!
An explosion?
Hey, just calm down.
Were you also in the blast?
I'm an office worker who was
nearby, but now I'm going to die!
I'm losing way too much blood!
Why me?
Hey, come on, man. Calm down.
It's gonna be alright.
I can heal you, lickety-split.
Alright, now tell me where it hurts most.
My midsection!
I think one of my rips might
have punctured my lung!
Please, hurry and save me!
Pretty, huh? That's weird.
Last time I checked, I looked like I was
just an ordinary high school student.
Yet you believed I
could treat your wounds.
I still have trouble getting people
to let me into pachinko parlors,
but somehow I strike you
as a med school graduate
ready and willing to fix
your little boo-boos?
Huh?
You totally took the bait,
which means you have the ability
to see my shining diamond.
Crap!
I got too excited!
That must make you the killer we're
after and they are your would-be victims
Wait, are you serious?
He's the killer?
It seems you finally hunted
down your culprit. You're right.
I'm the one you've been looking for
Morio's resident killer You know
my identity the true nature of my
stand you even know my real name?
I suppose sleeping like a baby
isn't really in the cards for me!
But it's just a temporary setback.
Deadly Queen!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
What does it look like I severed my hand?
It's so excruciating, it's a
wonder I'm still conscious.
There's so much blood, look
at me, I'm a sobbing mess.
Victory and defeat mean
absolutely nothing to me, kiddos.
I assure you I'll survive.
I'll live on in peaceful tranquility.
It's true I'll have to
live out the rest of
my days with the
insatiable desire to kill.
But make no mistake, I'll
have my happy ending.
I hereby free you, heart attack.
You may act as you see fit.
Your final duty is to protect me.
You're kidding me!
What is this toy gonna do?
Josuke, that's a remote bomb stand
set to go after thermal energy.
The thing is completely indestructible.
If it hits you, your body
temperature will set it off!
Shining diamond can't break the thing!
Break it?
Why the hell would I do that
when I can fix it instead?
He was kind enough to
leave his hand behind.
It's not the prettiest sight to look at,
but that hand is leading
us to our murderer.
Let's go! Yeah!
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY FROM US
THAT EASILY, YOU FREAKING PSYCHO!
Hey, you girls seeing this?
Mark my words, I'll do whatever it
takes to sleep peacefully again.
Kira, what happened?
Why is your face caked in blood?
Hi, everyone.
Is it time to head home already?
Sorry, but I'm in a hurry.
See you around.
The murderer's name is Yoshikage Kira.
His address is Mariah Kotodai 1128.
He's 33 years old.
Also, he wields a short-range
bomb stand called Deadly Queen.
Just look at it go!
Where's this guy running to?
It doesn't matter where he's going.
When we find him, he's dead.
He's holed up in this building.
Guys, wait a second.
Isn't this...
Beauty Institute Cinderella?
Why the hell would he
come to a place like this?
Oh no! Dr. Aya!
Aya, are you in here?
Dr. Aya! She's...
No way! It can't be!
The hell did she do to deserve this?
Look over there.
It's Yoshikage Kira.
He's dead.
Hiya!
This is awful.
What the hell could have happened in here?
Wait, that man isn't Yoshikage Kira.
He's got two hands.
Holy shit, his face is missing. What?
His fingerprints are too.
That's so weird.
Who is this guy?
He has the same height
and belt as the murderer.
That monster brought him here and murdered
the poor man right before my eyes.
He's more ghastly than I imagined.
He forced me to use Cinderella to replace
his face as well as his
hair and fingerprints.
Wait, are you saying
he's someone else now?
That's right.
His new face.
Shining diamonds!
His face.
No, Josuke, don't touch her.
Get back right now!
His face.
Kaya!
He's on the other side of that door.
He won't escape!
Oh, you're joking!
Everyone's going home!
There are so many!
But which one is he?
Which one of these guys is Yoshikage Kira?
Yoshikage Kira!
You gutless prick!
Come out here and face us!
So he managed to slip away.
With his new face he'll have
no reason to fear or hide.
You can bet your ass he'll
stay right here in Morioh,
and go on living just as he always has.
Aya Tsuji deceased.
Yoshikage Kira has changed his face, name,
and address and assumed a new identity.